100% PURE Privacy Policy                                                                                                         

My Tote
-------

  Close cart

SPEND $45 To

UNLOCK BEAUTY DEALS

BEAUTY DEALS UNLOCKED!

BEAUTY DEALS

Beauty Deal - Multi-Vitamin + Antioxidants PM Eye Treatment

SELECT Buy for $25

Beauty Deal - Multi-Vitamin + Antioxidants PM Eye Treatment

Richly moisturizing, vitamin concentrated eye treatment lessens the appearance of lines and wrinkles and increases firmness, elasticity, and brightens the eye area.

SELECT

Beauty Deal - Multi-Vitamin + Antioxidants PM Facial Oil

SELECT Buy for $25

Beauty Deal - Multi-Vitamin + Antioxidants PM Facial Oil

Age corrective visibly reduce lines, wrinkles + increase firmness and elasticity. A multi-vitamin facial oil treatment designed for targeted anti-aging benefits. Features concentrated potencies of vitamins E, C, D3, retinol and CoQ10.

SELECT

Beauty Deal - Multi-Vitamin + Antioxidants Ultra Riché PM Treatment

SELECT Buy for $25

Beauty Deal - Multi-Vitamin + Antioxidants Ultra Riché PM Treatment

Age Corrective. Luxurious night cream is a multi-vitamin powerhouse made with correcting vitamin C and reparative vitamin A, and works to combat daily damage and signs of aging.

SELECT

Beauty Deal - Multi-Vitamin + Antioxidants Potent PM Serum

SELECT Buy for $25

Beauty Deal - Multi-Vitamin + Antioxidants Potent PM Serum

Potent, stabilized vitamins in this PM serum work synergistically to reduce lines and wrinkles, increase firmness and elasticity, brighten and even skin tone.

SELECT

Beauty Deal - Bakuchiol Cleanser

SELECT Buy for $25

Beauty Deal - Bakuchiol Cleanser

Softening. This gentle yet powerful cleanser provides a safer and natural alternative to Retinol to stimulate cellular turnover for a smoother complexion, lighten age/sun spots for a more even skin tone and visibly lessen the appearance of lines and wrinkles.

SELECT

Beauty Deal - Bakuchiol Moisturizer

SELECT Buy for $25

Beauty Deal - Bakuchiol Moisturizer

This antioxidant rich, natural Retinol alternative, packs a gentle but powerful punch to soften and hydrate the skin. Formulated with deeply hydrating Hyaluronic Acid and Squalane, this powerful botanical stimulates cellular turnover, boosts collagen production, lightens age and sun spots while lessening the appearance of lines and wrinkles.

SELECT

Beauty Deal - Bakuchiol Oil Serum

SELECT Buy for $25

Beauty Deal - Bakuchiol Oil Serum

Plant Alternative to Retinol. This skin softening, moisture-magnet facial oil serum gives you the same benefits of retinol but in a gentler form. Bakuchiol stimulates cellular turnover for a smoother complexion, lightens age/sun spots for a more even skin tone and visibly lessens the appearance of lines and wrinkles.

SELECT

Beauty Deal - Mushroom Peptides Firming Serum

SELECT Buy for $25

Beauty Deal - Mushroom Peptides Firming Serum

Medicinal mushrooms deliver multiple skin benefits. Unlock firmer-looking skin with eleven different skin beneficial medicinal mushrooms and quinoa peptides that make skin more resilient, vibrant and increase firmness and elasticity.

SELECT

Beauty Deal - Mushroom Peptide Moisturizer

SELECT Buy for $25

Beauty Deal - Mushroom Peptide Moisturizer

A luxurious blend of 11 medicinal mushrooms, hyaluronic acid & quinoa peptides for intense hydration & firmness. Antioxidant-rich formula boosts skin's glow & vibrancy. Perfect for a youthful, radiant complexion.

SELECT

Beauty Deal - Retinol PM Eye Cream

SELECT Buy for $25

Beauty Deal - Retinol PM Eye Cream

Hydrating, potent concentration of anti-aging vitamins, stem cells, and peptides promotes collagen production, elasticity, and lessens appearance of wrinkles.

SELECT

Beauty Deal - Super Fruit Oil Nourishing Eye Cream

SOLD OUT Buy for $25

Beauty Deal - Super Fruit Oil Nourishing Eye Cream

Superfruit oils provide deep moisture, potent vitamins, and protective antioxidants to promote elasticity and lessen the appearance of lines and wrinkles.

SOLD OUT

Beauty Deal - Retinol Restorative Neck Cream

SELECT Buy for $25

Beauty Deal - Retinol Restorative Neck Cream

Promotes elasticity for a firmer, more lifted neck. Retinol reduces appearance of lines and wrinkles; olive squalane and hyaluronic acid enhance suppleness.

SELECT

Beauty Deal - Watermelon Cucumber Water Locking Serum

SELECT Buy for $25

Beauty Deal - Watermelon Cucumber Water Locking Serum

Intense Hydration. Intensely hydrating hydrogel serum locks in watermelon hydrosol to revitalize dehydrated skin cells with skin plumping polyglumatic acid from fermented natto beans and moisture retaining hyaluronic acid.

SELECT

Beauty Deal - Apple Enzyme Resurfacing Serum

SELECT Buy for $25

Beauty Deal - Apple Enzyme Resurfacing Serum

Re-Surfacing. Regenerative serum made with skin brightening licorice, kojic acid from sake (fermented rice), sugar alpha hydroxy acid, beet lactic acid and fruit enzymes from pineapple, green apple, citrus and papaya

SELECT

Beauty Deal - Black Tea Grass Jelly Anti-oxidant Serum

SELECT Buy for $25

Beauty Deal - Black Tea Grass Jelly Anti-oxidant Serum

Antioxidants Concentrated. Formulated with Puerh Black Tea Leaves, this serum is packed with antioxidants that protect skin from free radicals and is skin plumping and firming with an anti-aging effect. The quick-absorbing, formula hydrates and nourishes prepping your skin for perfect makeup application.

SELECT

Beauty Deal - Watermelon Cucumber Water Locking Moisturizer

SELECT Buy for $25

Beauty Deal - Watermelon Cucumber Water Locking Moisturizer

Intense Hydration. Hydrating moisturizer locks in watermelon hydrosol and polyglutamic acid to naturally restore skin elasticity, promote cell regeneration, and reduce signs of aging.

SELECT

Beauty Deal - Coffee Bean Caffeine Restorative Serum

SELECT Buy for $25

Beauty Deal - Coffee Bean Caffeine Restorative Serum

Protects + Repairs from UV Damage. A hydrating, restorative serum mirrored after our best selling Coffee Bean Caffeine Eye Cream. Reverse sun damage, brighten and tighten your skin for an immediate healthy, vibrant glow!

SELECT

Beauty Deal - Burdock and Neem Healthy Scalp Conditioner - 32oz

SELECT Buy for $25

Beauty Deal - Burdock and Neem Healthy Scalp Conditioner - 32oz

\[empty\]

SELECT

Beauty Deal - Burdock and Neem Healthy Scalp Shampoo - 32oz

SOLD OUT Buy for $25

Beauty Deal - Burdock and Neem Healthy Scalp Shampoo - 32oz

Purifying formula unclogs pores, stimulates circulation, and alleviates dryness, itching, and flaking. With added hydration for healthier scalp and hair.

SOLD OUT

Beauty Deal - Vitamin C Serum

SELECT Buy for $20

Beauty Deal - Vitamin C Serum

Lightweight, stabilized vitamin C serum helps firm and brighten skin tone while promoting collagen production, and deeply hydrating skin with soothing aloe.

SELECT

Beauty Deal - Acai Pulp Facial Scrub

SELECT Buy for $20

Beauty Deal - Acai Pulp Facial Scrub

Super fruit infused all natural facial scrub smoothes away bumps, flakes, and dead skin while instilling vitamins and antioxidants for a super soft, glowing complexion.

SELECT

Beauty Deal - Strawberry Brightening Scrub

SELECT Buy for $20

Beauty Deal - Strawberry Brightening Scrub

Berry brightening facial scrub made with puréed strawberry, pineapple, papaya, cranberry, bilberry, grape, lemon and orange blended together to feed your skin vitamins and antioxidants while gently smoothing away bumps and flakes for a super soft, glowing complexion!

SELECT

Beauty Deal - Blood Orange Cleansing Balm

SELECT Buy for $20

Beauty Deal - Blood Orange Cleansing Balm

Moisturizing facial cleanser made with degreasing blood orange, plus coconut and olive oils to sweep away even the most stubborn makeup, debris, and impurities.

SELECT

Beauty Deal - Retinol Restorative Overnight Balm

SOLD OUT Buy for $20

Beauty Deal - Retinol Restorative Overnight Balm

Nourishing PM balm enhances firmness, tone, and elasticity while you sleep. Made with vegan retinol, avocado butter, and plant oils to moisturize and restore.

SOLD OUT

Beauty Deal - Green Tea EGCG Concentrate Cream

SELECT Buy for $20

Beauty Deal - Green Tea EGCG Concentrate Cream

Highly nutrient-rich moisturizer softens and fortifies skin. EGCG, the potent antioxidant from green tea, protects against environmental damage.

SELECT

Beauty Deal - Green Tea EGCG Concentrate Serum

SELECT Buy for $20

Beauty Deal - Green Tea EGCG Concentrate Serum

Skin Protective Green Tea. Lightweight, hydrating serum concentrated with EGCG, the key antioxidant in green tea that can delay signs of aging, and caffeine to tone, brighten, and depuff.

SELECT

Beauty Deal - Fermented Rice Water Cleanser

SELECT Buy for $20

Beauty Deal - Fermented Rice Water Cleanser

Softening. Fermented rice water (Sake) is rich in enzymes, amino acids, malic acid, minerals, and vitamins to brighten, gently exfoliate, and deeply soften skin.

SELECT

Beauty Deal - Fermented Rice Water Toner

SELECT Buy for $20

Beauty Deal - Fermented Rice Water Toner

Softening. Brightening facial toner uses enzymes and amino acids from fermented rice water (Sake) to brighten, hydrate, plump, and deeply soften skin.

SELECT

Beauty Deal - Fermented Rice Water Serum

SELECT Buy for $20

Beauty Deal - Fermented Rice Water Serum

Concentrated daily serum is made with fermented rice water (Sake), which is rich in enzymes and beneficial nutrients to brighten, soften, and hydrate your skin.

SELECT

Beauty Deal - Fruit Pigmented® Rose Gold Palette

SELECT Buy for $20

Beauty Deal - Fruit Pigmented® Rose Gold Palette

A rose gold treasure trove of warm metallics and stunning shimmer. Deluxe fruit pigmented® palette includes a highlighter, blush, and 3 eye shadows.

SELECT

Beauty Deal - Fruit Pigmented Better Naked Palette

SELECT Buy for $20

Beauty Deal - Fruit Pigmented Better Naked Palette

Fruit Pigmented® makeup palette amplifies rosy, taupe, and beige toned nudes with shimmery, gilded metallics. Includes eyeshadows, blush, and highlighter.

SELECT

Beauty Deal - Fruit Pigmented® Berry Naked Palette

SELECT Buy for $20

Beauty Deal - Fruit Pigmented® Berry Naked Palette

Fruit Pigmented® berry eyeshadow palette of nude, blush, and metallic tones. Our vegan makeup palette includes eyeshadows, blush, and highlighter colored from fruit and vegetable pigments.

SELECT

Beauty Deal - Fruit Pigmented® Pretty Naked Palette

SELECT Buy for $20

Beauty Deal - Fruit Pigmented® Pretty Naked Palette

Fruit pigmented® makeup palette celebrates neutral tones and soft shimmer to enhance and beautify your complexion. Includes eyeshadows, blush, and highlighter.

SELECT

Beauty Deal - Luminous Primer

SELECT Buy for $20

Beauty Deal - Luminous Primer

Silicone-free, antioxidant infused primer diffuses pores and illuminates with light reflective pigment while giving flawless, long lasting cosmetic application.

SELECT

Beauty Deal - Mattifying Primer

SELECT Buy for $20

Beauty Deal - Mattifying Primer

Silicone-free primer infused with skin-plumping seaweed collagen for flawless, long lasting cosmetic application. Fills fine lines while minimizing shine.

SELECT

Beauty Deal - Cocoa Pigmented Bronzer - Cocoa Gem

SELECT Buy for $20

Beauty Deal - Cocoa Pigmented Bronzer - Cocoa Gem

Warm your complexion using vitamin-rich fruit and cocoa pigments, laced with luminescent gems and minerals for subtle shimmer and a sun-kissed glow.

SELECT

Beauty Deal - Cocoa Pigmented Bronzer - Cocoa Kissed

SELECT Buy for $20

Beauty Deal - Cocoa Pigmented Bronzer - Cocoa Kissed

Warm your complexion using vitamin-rich fruit and cocoa pigments, laced with luminescent gems and minerals for subtle shimmer and a sun-kissed glow.

SELECT

Beauty Deal - Cocoa Pigmented Bronzer: Cocoa Glow

SELECT Buy for $20

Beauty Deal - Cocoa Pigmented Bronzer: Cocoa Glow

Warm your complexion using vitamin-rich fruit and cocoa pigments, laced with luminescent gems and minerals for subtle shimmer and a sun-kissed glow.

SELECT

Beauty Deal - Fruit Pigmented Full Coverage Water Foundation: Cool 1.0

SELECT Buy for $20

Beauty Deal - Fruit Pigmented Full Coverage Water Foundation: Cool 1.0

Fruit pigmented® foundation plumps and hydrates skin with soothing aloe and toning green tea. Offers flawless full coverage with a satin, lightly dewy finish.

SELECT

Beauty Deal - Fruit Pigmented Full Coverage Water Foundation: Cool 3.0

SELECT Buy for $20

Beauty Deal - Fruit Pigmented Full Coverage Water Foundation: Cool 3.0

Fruit pigmented® foundation plumps and hydrates skin with soothing aloe and toning green tea. Offers flawless full coverage with a satin, lightly dewy finish.

SELECT

Beauty Deal - Fruit Pigmented® Full Coverage Water Foundation: Cool 4.0

SELECT Buy for $20

Beauty Deal - Fruit Pigmented® Full Coverage Water Foundation: Cool 4.0

Fruit pigmented® foundation plumps and hydrates skin with soothing aloe and toning green tea. Offers flawless full coverage with a satin, lightly dewy finish.

SELECT

Beauty Deal - Fruit Pigmented Full Coverage Water Foundation: Neutral 5.0

SELECT Buy for $20

Beauty Deal - Fruit Pigmented Full Coverage Water Foundation: Neutral 5.0

Fruit pigmented® foundation plumps and hydrates skin with soothing aloe and toning green tea. Offers flawless full coverage with a satin, lightly dewy finish.

SELECT

Beauty Deal - Fruit Pigmented Full Coverage Water Foundation: Warm 5.0

SELECT Buy for $20

Beauty Deal - Fruit Pigmented Full Coverage Water Foundation: Warm 5.0

Fruit pigmented® foundation plumps and hydrates skin with soothing aloe and toning green tea. Offers flawless full coverage with a satin, lightly dewy finish.

SELECT

Beauty Deal - Fruit Pigmented Full Coverage Water Foundation: Warm 8.0

SELECT Buy for $20

Beauty Deal - Fruit Pigmented Full Coverage Water Foundation: Warm 8.0

Fruit pigmented® foundation plumps and hydrates skin with soothing aloe and toning green tea. Offers flawless full coverage with a satin, lightly dewy finish.

SELECT

Beauty Deal - Rose Micellar Cleansing Water

SELECT Buy for $15

Beauty Deal - Rose Micellar Cleansing Water

Hydrating Makeup Remover. Hydrating cleansing water gently rinses away makeup, sunblock, excess oil, and environmental toxins while purifying and toning with calming floral waters.

SELECT

Beauty Deal - Rose Water Hyaluronic Acid Serum

SELECT Buy for $15

Beauty Deal - Rose Water Hyaluronic Acid Serum

Soothing + Hydrating. Deeply hydrating serum made with balancing rose hydrosol, calming calendula, and plumping hyaluronic acid.

SELECT

Beauty Deal - Rose Water Face Mist

SELECT Buy for $15

Beauty Deal - Rose Water Face Mist

Balancing natural rose water spray delivers a kiss of hydration from rose water and hyaluronic acid for a plumped, youthful glow.

SELECT

Beauty Deal - Rose Water Hydrating Milk

SELECT Buy for $15

Beauty Deal - Rose Water Hydrating Milk

Lightweight facial moisturizer made with rose hydrosol and hyaluronic acid to deeply calm, soften, and hydrate the skin.

SELECT

Beauty Deal - Restorative Sea Culture Extra Riche Creme

SELECT Buy for $15

Beauty Deal - Restorative Sea Culture Extra Riche Creme

Plumping. Rich, luxurious cream drenches skin in deep moisture, delivers nutrient-rich sea minerals and vitamins, and plumps skin with hydrating seaweed polysaccharides.

SELECT

Beauty Deal - Restorative Sea Culture Hydrating Toner

SELECT Buy for $15

Beauty Deal - Restorative Sea Culture Hydrating Toner

Skin Plumping. Water-drenching facial toner softens, plumps, and hydrates skin using a base of gelatinous algin from mineral-rich seaweed sourced from pure, unpolluted waters.

SELECT

---

### [Coffee Bean Caffeine Brightening Eye Cream](https://www.100percentpure.com/products/coffee-bean-caffeine-brightening-eye-cream)

4630 reviews (4630)

$23.00 $42.00

1 oz - $42 0.3 oz - $23

1 oz

0.3 oz

ADD TO TOTE

CHOOSE Size

### [Multi-Vitamin + Antioxidants Ultra Riché PM Treatment](https://www.100percentpure.com/products/multi-vitamin-antioxidants-ultra-riche-pm-treatment)

1049 reviews (1049)

$92.00

Default Title - $92

ADD TO TOTE

### [Multi-Vitamin + Antioxidants Potent PM Serum](https://www.100percentpure.com/products/multi-vitamin-antioxidants-potent-pm-serums)

101 reviews (101)

$104.00

1 oz - $104

ADD TO TOTE

### [Maracuja Mascara](https://www.100percentpure.com/products/maracuja-mascara)

2417 reviews (2417)

$41.00 $41.00

Dark Chocolate - $41 Blackberry - $41 Black Tea - $41

Black Tea

Blackberry

Dark Chocolate

CHOOSE Color

### [Coconut Nourishing Body Cream](https://www.100percentpure.com/products/coconut-nourishing-body-cream)

763 reviews (763)

$18.00 $38.00

1.7 oz - $18 8 oz - $38

8 oz

1.7 oz

ADD TO TOTE

CHOOSE Size

### [Collagen Boost Sheet Mask](https://www.100percentpure.com/products/sheet-mask-collagen-boost-masks)

39 reviews (39)

$11.00 $41.00

Single - $11 5 Pack - $41

Single

5 Pack

ADD TO TOTE

CHOOSE Size

### [Deep Hydration Sheet Mask](https://www.100percentpure.com/products/sheet-mask-deep-hydration-masks)

375 reviews (375)

$11.00

Single - $11

ADD TO TOTE

### [Creamy Long Last Liner](https://www.100percentpure.com/products/creamy-long-last-liner)

2029 reviews (2029)

$39.00 $39.00

Blackest - $39 Gleaming Pewter - $39 Dark Cacao - $39

Gleaming Pewter

Blackest

Dark Cacao

ADD TO TOTE

CHOOSE Color

### [Watermelon Cucumber Water Locking Mist](https://www.100percentpure.com/products/watermelon-cucumber-water-locking-mist)

46 reviews (46)

$36.00

Default Title - $36

ADD TO TOTE

### [Does It All Sheet Mask](https://www.100percentpure.com/products/sheet-mask-does-it-all-masks)

370 reviews (370)

$11.00 $46.00

Single - $11 5 Pack - $46

5 Pack

Single

ADD TO TOTE

CHOOSE Size

### [Acai Pulp Facial Scrub](https://www.100percentpure.com/products/acai-pulp-facial-scrub)

846 reviews (846)

$55.00

Default Title - $55

ADD TO TOTE

### [Multi-Vitamin + Antioxidants PM Facial Oil](https://www.100percentpure.com/products/multi-vitamin-antioxidants-pm-facial-oil)

197 reviews (197)

$84.00

Default Title - $84

ADD TO TOTE

### [Blood Orange Nourishing Body Cream](https://www.100percentpure.com/products/blood-orange-nourishing-body-cream)

297 reviews (297)

$38.00

Default Title - $38

ADD TO TOTE

### [French Lavender Nourishing Body Cream](https://www.100percentpure.com/products/french-lavender-nourishing-body-cream)

350 reviews (350)

$38.00

Default Title - $38

ADD TO TOTE

### [Honey Almond Nourishing Body Cream](https://www.100percentpure.com/products/honey-almond-nourishing-body-cream)

387 reviews (387)

$38.00

Default Title - $38

ADD TO TOTE

### [Cucumber Cloud Foam Cleanser](https://www.100percentpure.com/products/cucumber-cloud-foam-cleanser)

120 reviews (120)

$44.00

Default Title - $44

ADD TO TOTE

### [Blood Orange Cleansing Balm](https://www.100percentpure.com/products/blood-orange-cleansing-balm)

880 reviews (880)

$55.00

Default Title - $55

ADD TO TOTE

### [Long Last Liquid Eye Liner](https://www.100percentpure.com/products/long-last-liquid-eye-liner)

1574 reviews (1574)

$44.00 $44.00

Blackberry - $44 Black Tea - $44 Dark Chocolate - $44

Black Tea

Blackberry

Dark Chocolate

ADD TO TOTE

CHOOSE Color

### [Mattifying Primer](https://www.100percentpure.com/products/mattifying-primer)

1136 reviews (1136)

$65.00

Default Title - $65

ADD TO TOTE

### [Hydra Drench Cream](https://www.100percentpure.com/products/hydra-drench-cream)

513 reviews (513)

$69.00

Default Title - $69

ADD TO TOTE

### [Dark Spot Remover](https://www.100percentpure.com/products/dark-spot-remover)

545 reviews (545)

$75.00

Default Title - $75

ADD TO TOTE

### [Watermelon Cucumber Water Locking Serum](https://www.100percentpure.com/products/watermelon-cucumber-water-locking-serum)

59 reviews (59)

$69.00

Default Title - $69

ADD TO TOTE

### [Vitamin C Serum](https://www.100percentpure.com/products/vitamin-c-serum)

1422 reviews (1422)

$84.00

Default Title - $84

ADD TO TOTE

### [Bakuchiol Moisturizer](https://www.100percentpure.com/products/bakuchiol-moisturizer)

189 reviews (189)

$84.00

Default Title - $84

ADD TO TOTE

### [Fruit Pigmented® Ultra Lengthening Mascara](https://www.100percentpure.com/products/fruit-pigmented-ultra-lengthening-mascara)

5301 reviews (5301)

$41.00 $41.00

Blackberry - $41 Blueberry - $41 Black Tea - $41 Dark Chocolate - $41

Blueberry

Black Tea

Blackberry

Dark Chocolate

ADD TO TOTE

CHOOSE Color

### [Coffee Bean Caffeine Restorative Moisturizer](https://www.100percentpure.com/products/coffee-bean-caffeine-restorative-moisturizer)

127 reviews (127)

$80.00

Default Title - $80

ADD TO TOTE

### [Apple Enzyme Resurfacing Serum](https://www.100percentpure.com/products/apple-enzyme-resurfacing-serum)

84 reviews (84)

$69.00

Default Title - $69

ADD TO TOTE

### [Apple Enzyme Exfoliating Cleanser](https://www.100percentpure.com/products/apple-enzyme-exfoliating-cleanser)

83 reviews (83)

$46.00

Default Title - $46

ADD TO TOTE

### [Organic Mint Lip Balm](https://www.100percentpure.com/products/organic-mint-lip-balm)

521 reviews (521)

$12.00

Default Title - $12

ADD TO TOTE

### [Bright Eyes Masks](https://www.100percentpure.com/products/bright-eyes-masks)

977 reviews (977)

$11.00 $44.00

5 Pack - $44 Single - $11

Single

5 Pack

ADD TO TOTE

CHOOSE Size

### [Cherry Lip Balm](https://www.100percentpure.com/products/cherry-lip-balm)

759 reviews (759)

$12.00

Default Title - $12

ADD TO TOTE

### [Watermelon Cucumber Water Locking Moisturizer](https://www.100percentpure.com/products/watermelon-cucumber-water-locking-moisturizer)

103 reviews (103)

$80.00

Default Title - $80

ADD TO TOTE

### [Green Tea EGCG Concentrate Cream](https://www.100percentpure.com/products/green-tea-egcg-concentrate-cream)

697 reviews (697)

$69.00

Default Title - $69

ADD TO TOTE

### [Ginseng Collagen Boost Mask](https://www.100percentpure.com/products/ginseng-collagen-boost-masks)

503 reviews (503)

$12.00

Single - $12

ADD TO TOTE

### [Green Tea Water Bomb Mask](https://www.100percentpure.com/products/green-tea-water-bomb-masks)

464 reviews (464)

$12.00

Single - $12

ADD TO TOTE

Subtotal

$0.00

##### $0.00

Get 20% Off on Your Birthday!

Taxes and shipping calculated at checkout

Checkout

or 4 interest-free payments of **$0.00** with 

[🎉 Annual Beauty Deals Sale is LIVE! Prices start at just $5 with up to 70% OFF. Shop now before it's gone!](https://www.100percentpure.com/collections/beauty-deals "https://www.100percentpure.com/collections/beauty-deals")

icon-account icon-account icon-arrow-right icon-arrow-down icon-arrow-next icon-arrow-prev icon-slideshow-next icon-slideshow-previous icon-comment icon-heart icon-cart icon-bag icon-close icon-glasses icon-menu icon-minus icon-play icon-plus social-seach social-facebook social-fancy social-instagram social-pinterest social-rss social-twitter

    #### [FEATURED](https://www.100percentpure.com/)

    #### [Product Type](#)

    #### [Ph](https://www.100percentpure.com/)

    [
    
    Makeup Best Sellers](https://www.100percentpure.com/collections/fruit-dyed-makeup/?sort_by=best-selling)
    
    [
    
    Skin Care Best Sellers](https://www.100percentpure.com/collections/skin-care/?sort_by=best-selling)

    #### [ABOUT](https://www.100percentpure.com/pages/about-us)

    #### [LEARN](#)

    #### [Ph2](#)

    [
    
    Product Quizzes](https://www.100percentpure.com/pages/product-finder)
    
    [
    
    From Our Blog](https://www.100percentpure.com/blogs/feed#cover)

----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------

* Search 

100% PURE Privacy Policy
========================

**Last updated July 20, 2022**

This privacy notice for Purity Cosmetics (doing business as 100% Pure) ("**100% Pure**," "**we**," "**us**," or "**our**"), describes how and why we might collect, store, use, and/or share ("**process**") your information when you use our services ("**Services**"), such as when you:

* Visit our website at 100percentpure.com, or any website of ours that links to this privacy notice

* Engage with us in other related ways, including any sales, marketing, or events

**Questions or concerns?** Reading this privacy notice will help you understand your privacy rights and choices. If you do not agree with our policies and practices, please do not use our Services. If you still have any questions or concerns, please contact us at [\[email protected\]](https://www.100percentpure.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection).

**SUMMARY OF KEY POINTS**

**_This summary provides key points from our privacy notice, but you can find out more details about any of these topics by clicking the link following each key point or by using our table of contents below to find the section you are looking for. You can also click_** [**_here_**](#toc) **_to go directly to our table of contents._**

**What personal information do we process?** When you visit, use, or navigate our Services, we may process personal information depending on how you interact with 100% Pure and the Services, the choices you make, and the products and features you use. Click [here](#personalinfo) to learn more.

**Do we process any sensitive personal information?** We do not process sensitive personal information.

**Do we receive any information from third parties?** We do not receive any information from third parties.

**How do we process your information?** We process your information to provide, improve, and administer our Services, communicate with you, for security and fraud prevention, and to comply with law. We may also process your information for other purposes with your consent. We process your information only when we have a valid legal reason to do so. Click [here](#infouse) to learn more.

**In what situations and with which types of parties do we share personal information?** We may share information in specific situations and with specific categories of third parties. Click [here](#whoshare) to learn more.

**How do we keep your information safe?** We have organizational and technical processes and procedures in place to protect your personal information. However, no electronic transmission over the internet or information storage technology can be guaranteed to be 100% secure, so we cannot promise or guarantee that hackers, cybercriminals, or other unauthorized third parties will not be able to defeat our security and improperly collect, access, steal, or modify your information. Click [here](#infosafe) to learn more.

**What are your rights?** Depending on where you are located geographically, the applicable privacy law may mean you have certain rights regarding your personal information. Click [here](#privacyrights) to learn more.

**How do you exercise your rights?** The easiest way to exercise your rights is by filling out our data subject request form available here: [https://www.100percentpure.com/pages/dsar](https://www.100percentpure.com/pages/dsar), or by contacting us. We will consider and act upon any request in accordance with applicable data protection laws.

Want to learn more about what 100% Pure does with any information we collect? Click [here](#toc) to review the notice in full.

**TABLE OF CONTENTS**

[3\. WHAT LEGAL BASES DO WE RELY ON TO PROCESS YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?](#legalbases)

[4\. WHEN AND WITH WHOM DO WE SHARE YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?](#whoshare)

[15\. HOW CAN YOU REVIEW, UPDATE, OR DELETE THE DATA WE COLLECT FROM YOU?](#request)

**1\. WHAT INFORMATION DO WE COLLECT?**

**Personal information you disclose to us**

**_In Short:_** _We collect personal information that you provide to us._

We collect personal information that you voluntarily provide to us when you register on the Services, express an interest in obtaining information about us or our products and Services, when you participate in activities on the Services, or otherwise when you contact us.

**Personal Information Provided by You.** The personal information that we collect depends on the context of your interactions with us and the Services, the choices you make, and the products and features you use. The personal information we collect may include the following:

* names

* phone numbers

* email addresses

* mailing addresses

* billing addresses

**Sensitive Information.** We do not process sensitive information.

**Payment Data.** We may collect data necessary to process your payment if you make purchases, such as your payment instrument number (such as a credit card number), and the security code associated with your payment instrument. All payment data is stored by Shopify, PayPal, Amazon, AfterPay and Reach. You may find their privacy notice link(s) here: [https://www.shopify.com/legal/privacy/customers](https://www.shopify.com/legal/privacy/customers), [https://www.paypal.com/us/webapps/mpp/ua/privacy-full](https://www.paypal.com/us/webapps/mpp/ua/privacy-full), [https://pay.amazon.com/help/201751600](https://pay.amazon.com/help/201751600), [https://www.afterpay.com/privacy-policy](https://www.afterpay.com/privacy-policy) and [https://withreach.com/privacy-policy](https://withreach.com/privacy-policy).

**Social Media Login Data.** We may provide you with the option to register with us using your existing social media account details, like your Facebook, Twitter, or other social media account. If you choose to register in this way, we will collect the information described in the section called "[HOW DO WE HANDLE YOUR SOCIAL LOGINS?](#sociallogins)" below.

All personal information that you provide to us must be true, complete, and accurate, and you must notify us of any changes to such personal information.

**Information automatically collected**

**_In Short:_** _Some information — such as your Internet Protocol (IP) address and/or browser and device characteristics — is collected automatically when you visit our Services._

We automatically collect certain information when you visit, use, or navigate the Services. This information does not reveal your specific identity (like your name or contact information) but may include device and usage information, such as your IP address, browser and device characteristics, operating system, language preferences, referring URLs, device name, country, location, information about how and when you use our Services, and other technical information. This information is primarily needed to maintain the security and operation of our Services, and for our internal analytics and reporting purposes.

Like many businesses, we also collect information through cookies and similar technologies. You can find out more about this in our Cookie Notice: [https://www.100percentpure.com/pages/cookie-policy](https://www.100percentpure.com/pages/cookie-policy).

The information we collect includes:

* _Log and Usage Data._ Log and usage data is service-related, diagnostic, usage, and performance information our servers automatically collect when you access or use our Services and which we record in log files. Depending on how you interact with us, this log data may include your IP address, device information, browser type, and settings and information about your activity in the Services (such as the date/time stamps associated with your usage, pages and files viewed, searches, and other actions you take such as which features you use), device event information (such as system activity, error reports (sometimes called "crash dumps"), and hardware settings).

* _Device Data._ We collect device data such as information about your computer, phone, tablet, or other device you use to access the Services. Depending on the device used, this device data may include information such as your IP address (or proxy server), device and application identification numbers, location, browser type, hardware model, Internet service provider and/or mobile carrier, operating system, and system configuration information.

* _Location Data._ We collect location data such as information about your device's location, which can be either precise or imprecise. How much information we collect depends on the type and settings of the device you use to access the Services. For example, we may use GPS and other technologies to collect geolocation data that tells us your current location (based on your IP address). You can opt out of allowing us to collect this information either by refusing access to the information or by disabling your Location setting on your device. However, if you choose to opt out, you may not be able to use certain aspects of the Services.

**2\. HOW DO WE PROCESS YOUR INFORMATION?**

**_In Short:_** _We process your information to provide, improve, and administer our Services, communicate with you, for security and fraud prevention, and to comply with law. We may also process your information for other purposes with your consent._

**We process your personal information for a variety of reasons, depending on how you interact with our Services, including:**

* **To facilitate account creation and authentication and otherwise manage user accounts.** We may process your information so you can create and log in to your account, as well as keep your account in working order.

* **To deliver and facilitate delivery of services to the user.** We may process your information to provide you with the requested service.

* **To respond to user inquiries/offer support to users.** We may process your information to respond to your inquiries and solve any potential issues you might have with the requested service.

* **To send administrative information to you.** We may process your information to send you details about our products and services, changes to our terms and policies, and other similar information.

* **To fulfill and manage your orders.** We may process your information to fulfill and manage your orders, payments, returns, and exchanges made through the Services.

* **To enable user-to-user communications.** We may process your information if you choose to use any of our offerings that allow for communication with another user.

* **To request feedback.** We may process your information when necessary to request feedback and to contact you about your use of our Services.

* **To send you marketing and promotional communications.** We may process the personal information you send to us for our marketing purposes, if this is in accordance with your marketing preferences. You can opt out of our marketing emails at any time. For more information, see "[WHAT ARE YOUR PRIVACY RIGHTS?](#privacyrights)" below).

* **To deliver targeted advertising to you.** We may process your information to develop and display personalized content and advertising tailored to your interests, location, and more. For more information see our Cookie Notice: [https://www.100percentpure.com/pages/cookie-policy](https://www.100percentpure.com/pages/cookie-policy).

* **To identify usage trends.** We may process information about how you use our Services to better understand how they are being used so we can improve them.

* **To determine the effectiveness of our marketing and promotional campaigns.** We may process your information to better understand how to provide marketing and promotional campaigns that are most relevant to you.

* **To save or protect an individual's vital interest.** We may process your information when necessary to save or protect an individual’s vital interest, such as to prevent harm.

**3\. WHAT LEGAL BASES DO WE RELY ON TO PROCESS YOUR INFORMATION?**

_**In Short:** We only process your personal information when we believe it is necessary and we have a valid legal reason (i.e., legal basis) to do so under applicable law, like with your consent, to comply with laws, to provide you with services to enter into or fulfill our contractual obligations, to protect your rights, or to fulfill our legitimate business interests._

_**If you are located in the EU or UK, this section applies to you.**_

The General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) and UK GDPR require us to explain the valid legal bases we rely on in order to process your personal information. As such, we may rely on the following legal bases to process your personal information:

* **Consent.** We may process your information if you have given us permission (i.e., consent) to use your personal information for a specific purpose. You can withdraw your consent at any time. Click [here](#withdrawconsent) to learn more.

* **Performance of a Contract.** We may process your personal information when we believe it is necessary to fulfill our contractual obligations to you, including providing our Services or at your request prior to entering into a contract with you.

* **Legitimate Interests.** We may process your information when we believe it is reasonably necessary to achieve our legitimate business interests and those interests do not outweigh your interests and fundamental rights and freedoms. For example, we may process your personal information for some of the purposes described in order to:

* Send users information about special offers and discounts on our products and services

* Develop and display personalized and relevant advertising content for our users

* Analyze how our services are used so we can improve them to engage and retain users

* Support our marketing activities

* Understand how our users use our products and services so we can improve user experience

* **Legal Obligations.** We may process your information where we believe it is necessary for compliance with our legal obligations, such as to cooperate with a law enforcement body or regulatory agency, exercise or defend our legal rights, or disclose your information as evidence in litigation in which we are involved.  

* **Vital Interests.** We may process your information where we believe it is necessary to protect your vital interests or the vital interests of a third party, such as situations involving potential threats to the safety of any person.

In legal terms, we are generally the "data controller" under European data protection laws of the personal information described in this privacy notice, since we determine the means and/or purposes of the data processing we perform. This privacy notice does not apply to the personal information we process as a "data processor" on behalf of our customers. In those situations, the customer that we provide services to and with whom we have entered into a data processing agreement is the "data controller" responsible for your personal information, and we merely process your information on their behalf in accordance with your instructions. If you want to know more about our customers' privacy practices, you should read their privacy policies and direct any questions you have to them.

**_If you are located in Canada, this section applies to you._**

We may process your information if you have given us specific permission (i.e., express consent) to use your personal information for a specific purpose, or in situations where your permission can be inferred (i.e., implied consent). You can withdraw your consent at any time. Click [here](#withdrawconsent) to learn more.

In some exceptional cases, we may be legally permitted under applicable law to process your information without your consent, including, for example:

* If collection is clearly in the interests of an individual and consent cannot be obtained in a timely way

* For investigations and fraud detection and prevention

* For business transactions provided certain conditions are met

* If it is contained in a witness statement and the collection is necessary to assess, process, or settle an insurance claim

* For identifying injured, ill, or deceased persons and communicating with next of kin

* If we have reasonable grounds to believe an individual has been, is, or may be victim of financial abuse

* If it is reasonable to expect collection and use with consent would compromise the availability or the accuracy of the information and the collection is reasonable for purposes related to investigating a breach of an agreement or a contravention of the laws of Canada or a province

* If disclosure is required to comply with a subpoena, warrant, court order, or rules of the court relating to the production of records

* If it was produced by an individual in the course of their employment, business, or profession and the collection is consistent with the purposes for which the information was produced

* If the collection is solely for journalistic, artistic, or literary purposes

* If the information is publicly available and is specified by the regulations

**4\. WHEN AND WITH WHOM DO WE SHARE YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?**

**_In Short:_** _We may share information in specific situations described in this section and/or with the following categories of third parties._

**Vendors, Consultants, and Other Third-Party Service Providers.** We may share your data with third-party vendors, service providers, contractors, or agents ("**third parties**") who perform services for us or on our behalf and require access to such information to do that work. We have contracts in place with our third parties, which are designed to help safeguard your personal information. This means that they cannot do anything with your personal information unless we have instructed them to do it. They will also not share your personal information with any organization apart from us. They also commit to protect the data they hold on our behalf and to retain it for the period we instruct. The categories of third parties we may share personal information with are as follows:

* Affiliate Marketing Programs

* Data Analytics Services

* Order Fulfillment Service Providers

* Retargeting Platforms

* Sales & Marketing Tools

* Social Networks

We also may need to share your personal information in the following situations:

* **Business Transfers.** We may share or transfer your information in connection with, or during negotiations of, any merger, sale of company assets, financing, or acquisition of all or a portion of our business to another company.

* **Affiliates.** We may share your information with our affiliates, in which case we will require those affiliates to honor this privacy notice. Affiliates include our parent company and any subsidiaries, joint venture partners, or other companies that we control or that are under common control with us.

* **Business Partners.** We may share your information with our business partners to offer you certain products, services, or promotions.

The above excludes text messaging originator opt-in data and consent; this information will not be shared with any third parties.

**5\. DO WE USE COOKIES AND OTHER TRACKING TECHNOLOGIES?**

**_In Short:_** _We may use cookies and other tracking technologies to collect and store your information._

We may use cookies and similar tracking technologies (like web beacons and pixels) to access or store information. Specific information about how we use such technologies and how you can refuse certain cookies is set out in our Cookie Notice: [https://www.100percentpure.com/pages/cookie-policy](https://www.100percentpure.com/pages/cookie-policy).

**6\. HOW DO WE HANDLE YOUR SOCIAL LOGINS?**

**_In Short:_** _If you choose to register or log in to our services using a social media account, we may have access to certain information about you._

Our Services offer you the ability to register and log in using your third-party social media account details (like your Facebook or Twitter logins). Where you choose to do this, we will receive certain profile information about you from your social media provider. The profile information we receive may vary depending on the social media provider concerned, but will often include your name, email address, friends list, and profile picture, as well as other information you choose to make public on such a social media platform.

We will use the information we receive only for the purposes that are described in this privacy notice or that are otherwise made clear to you on the relevant Services. Please note that we do not control, and are not responsible for, other uses of your personal information by your third-party social media provider. We recommend that you review their privacy notice to understand how they collect, use, and share your personal information, and how you can set your privacy preferences on their sites and apps.

**7\. HOW LONG DO WE KEEP YOUR INFORMATION?**

**_In Short:_** _We keep your information for as long as necessary to fulfill the purposes outlined in this privacy notice unless otherwise required by law._

We will only keep your personal information for as long as it is necessary for the purposes set out in this privacy notice, unless a longer retention period is required or permitted by law (such as tax, accounting, or other legal requirements). No purpose in this notice will require us keeping your personal information for longer than the period of time in which users have an account with us.

When we have no ongoing legitimate business need to process your personal information, we will either delete or anonymize such information, or, if this is not possible (for example, because your personal information has been stored in backup archives), then we will securely store your personal information and isolate it from any further processing until deletion is possible.

**8\. HOW DO WE KEEP YOUR INFORMATION SAFE?**

**_In Short:_** _We aim to protect your personal information through a system of organizational and technical security measures._

We have implemented appropriate and reasonable technical and organizational security measures designed to protect the security of any personal information we process. However, despite our safeguards and efforts to secure your information, no electronic transmission over the Internet or information storage technology can be guaranteed to be 100% secure, so we cannot promise or guarantee that hackers, cybercriminals, or other unauthorized third parties will not be able to defeat our security and improperly collect, access, steal, or modify your information. Although we will do our best to protect your personal information, transmission of personal information to and from our Services is at your own risk. You should only access the Services within a secure environment.

**9\. DO WE COLLECT INFORMATION FROM MINORS?**

**_In Short:_** _We do not knowingly collect data from or market to children under 18 years of age._

We do not knowingly solicit data from or market to children under 18 years of age. By using the Services, you represent that you are at least 18 or that you are the parent or guardian of such a minor and consent to such minor dependent’s use of the Services. If we learn that personal information from users less than 18 years of age has been collected, we will deactivate the account and take reasonable measures to promptly delete such data from our records. If you become aware of any data we may have collected from children under age 18, please contact us at [\[email protected\]](https://www.100percentpure.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection).

**10\. WHAT ARE YOUR PRIVACY RIGHTS?**

**_In Short:_** _In some regions, such as the European Economic Area (EEA), United Kingdom (UK), and Canada, you have rights that allow you greater access to and control over your personal information. You may review, change, or terminate your account at any time._

In some regions (like the EEA, UK, and Canada), you have certain rights under applicable data protection laws. These may include the right (i) to request access and obtain a copy of your personal information, (ii) to request rectification or erasure; (iii) to restrict the processing of your personal information; and (iv) if applicable, to data portability. In certain circumstances, you may also have the right to object to the processing of your personal information. You can make such a request by contacting us by using the contact details provided in the section "[HOW CAN YOU CONTACT US ABOUT THIS NOTICE?](#contact)" below.

We will consider and act upon any request in accordance with applicable data protection laws.

If you are located in the EEA or UK and you believe we are unlawfully processing your personal information, you also have the right to complain to your local data protection supervisory authority. You can find their contact details here: [https://ec.europa.eu/justice/data-protection/bodies/authorities/index\_en.htm](https://ec.europa.eu/justice/data-protection/bodies/authorities/index_en.htm).

If you are located in Switzerland, the contact details for the data protection authorities are available here: [https://www.edoeb.admin.ch/edoeb/en/home.html](https://www.edoeb.admin.ch/edoeb/en/home.html).

**Withdrawing your consent:** If we are relying on your consent to process your personal information, which may be express and/or implied consent depending on the applicable law, you have the right to withdraw your consent at any time. You can withdraw your consent at any time by contacting us by using the contact details provided in the section "[HOW CAN YOU CONTACT US ABOUT THIS NOTICE?](#contact)" below.

However, please note that this will not affect the lawfulness of the processing before its withdrawal, nor when applicable law allows, will it affect the processing of your personal information conducted in reliance on lawful processing grounds other than consent.

**Opting out of marketing and promotional communications:** You can unsubscribe from our marketing and promotional communications at any time by clicking on the unsubscribe link in the emails that we send, replying "STOP" or "UNSUBSCRIBE" to the SMS messages that we send, or by contacting us using the details provided in the section "[HOW CAN YOU CONTACT US ABOUT THIS NOTICE?](#contact)" below. You will then be removed from the marketing lists. However, we may still communicate with you — for example, to send you service-related messages that are necessary for the administration and use of your account, to respond to service requests, or for other non-marketing purposes.

**Account Information**

If you would at any time like to review or change the information in your account or terminate your account, you can:

* Contact us using the contact information provided.

Upon your request to terminate your account, we will deactivate or delete your account and information from our active databases. However, we may retain some information in our files to prevent fraud, troubleshoot problems, assist with any investigations, enforce our legal terms and/or comply with applicable legal requirements.

**Cookies and similar technologies:** Most Web browsers are set to accept cookies by default. If you prefer, you can usually choose to set your browser to remove cookies and to reject cookies. If you choose to remove cookies or reject cookies, this could affect certain features or services of our Services. To opt out of interest-based advertising by advertisers on our Services visit [http://www.aboutads.info/choices/](http://www.aboutads.info/choices/). For further information, please see our Cookie Notice: [https://www.100percentpure.com/pages/cookie-policy](https://www.100percentpure.com/pages/cookie-policy).

If you have questions or comments about your privacy rights, you may email us at [\[email protected\]](https://www.100percentpure.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection).

**11\. CONTROLS FOR DO-NOT-TRACK FEATURES**

Most web browsers and some mobile operating systems and mobile applications include a Do-Not-Track ("DNT") feature or setting you can activate to signal your privacy preference not to have data about your online browsing activities monitored and collected. At this stage no uniform technology standard for recognizing and implementing DNT signals has been finalized. As such, we do not currently respond to DNT browser signals or any other mechanism that automatically communicates your choice not to be tracked online. If a standard for online tracking is adopted that we must follow in the future, we will inform you about that practice in a revised version of this privacy notice.

**12\. DO CALIFORNIA RESIDENTS HAVE SPECIFIC PRIVACY RIGHTS?**

**_In Short:_** _Yes, if you are a resident of California, you are granted specific rights regarding access to your personal information._

California Civil Code Section 1798.83, also known as the "Shine The Light" law, permits our users who are California residents to request and obtain from us, once a year and free of charge, information about categories of personal information (if any) we disclosed to third parties for direct marketing purposes and the names and addresses of all third parties with which we shared personal information in the immediately preceding calendar year. If you are a California resident and would like to make such a request, please submit your request in writing to us using the contact information provided below.

If you are under 18 years of age, reside in California, and have a registered account with Services, you have the right to request removal of unwanted data that you publicly post on the Services. To request removal of such data, please contact us using the contact information provided below and include the email address associated with your account and a statement that you reside in California. We will make sure the data is not publicly displayed on the Services, but please be aware that the data may not be completely or comprehensively removed from all our systems (e.g., backups, etc.).

**CCPA Privacy Notice**

The California Code of Regulations defines a "resident" as:

(1) every individual who is in the State of California for other than a temporary or transitory purpose and

(2) every individual who is domiciled in the State of California who is outside the State of California for a temporary or transitory purpose

All other individuals are defined as "non-residents."

If this definition of "resident" applies to you, we must adhere to certain rights and obligations regarding your personal information.

**What categories of personal information do we collect?**

We have collected the following categories of personal information in the past twelve (12) months:

|     |     |     |
| --- | --- | --- |
| **Category** | **Examples** | **Collected** |
| A. Identifiers | Contact details, such as real name, alias, postal address, telephone or mobile contact number, unique personal identifier, online identifier, Internet Protocol address, email address, and account name | YES |
| B. Personal information categories listed in the California Customer Records statute | Name, contact information, education, employment, employment history, and financial information | YES |
| C. Protected classification characteristics under California or federal law | Gender and date of birth | YES |
| D. Commercial information | Transaction information, purchase history, financial details, and payment information | YES |
| E. Biometric information | Fingerprints and voiceprints | NO  |
| F. Internet or other similar network activity | Browsing history, search history, online behavior, interest data, and interactions with our and other websites, applications, systems, and advertisements | YES |
| G. Geolocation data | Device location | YES |
| H. Audio, electronic, visual, thermal, olfactory, or similar information | Images and audio, video or call recordings created in connection with our business activities | YES |
| I. Professional or employment-related information | Business contact details in order to provide you our services at a business level or job title, work history, and professional qualifications if you apply for a job with us | NO  |
| J. Education Information | Student records and directory information | NO  |
| K. Inferences drawn from other personal information | Inferences drawn from any of the collected personal information listed above to create a profile or summary about, for example, an individual’s preferences and characteristics | NO  |

We may also collect other personal information outside of these categories instances where you interact with us in person, online, or by phone or mail in the context of:

* Receiving help through our customer support channels;

* Participation in customer surveys or contests; and

* Facilitation in the delivery of our Services and to respond to your inquiries.

**How do we use and share your personal information?**

Purity Cosmetics collects and shares your personal information through:

* Targeting cookies/Marketing cookies

More information about our data collection and sharing practices can be found in this privacy notice and our Cookie Notice: [https://www.100percentpure.com/pages/cookie-policy](https://www.100percentpure.com/pages/cookie-policy).

You may contact us by email at [\[email protected\]](https://www.100percentpure.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection), by visiting [https://www.100percentpure.com/pages/dsar-ccpa](https://www.100percentpure.com/pages/dsar-ccpa), or by referring to the contact details at the bottom of this document.

If you are using an authorized agent to exercise your right to opt out we may deny a request if the authorized agent does not submit proof that they have been validly authorized to act on your behalf.

**Will your information be shared with anyone else?**

We may disclose your personal information with our service providers pursuant to a written contract between us and each service provider. Each service provider is a for-profit entity that processes the information on our behalf.

We may use your personal information for our own business purposes, such as for undertaking internal research for technological development and demonstration. This is not considered to be "selling" of your personal information.

Purity Cosmetics has not sold any personal information to third parties for a business or commercial purpose in the preceding twelve (12) months. Purity Cosmetics has disclosed the following categories of personal information to third parties for a business or commercial purpose in the preceding twelve (12) months:

* Category A. Identifiers, such as contact details like your real name, alias, postal address, telephone or mobile contact number, unique personal identifier, online identifier, Internet Protocol address, email address, and account name.

* Category B. Personal information, as defined in the California Customer Records law, such as your name, contact information, education, employment, employment history, and financial information.

* Category C. Characteristics of protected classifications under California or federal law, such as gender or date of birth.

* Category D. Commercial information, such as transaction information, purchase history, financial details, and payment information.

* Category F. Internet or other electronic network activity information, such as browsing history, search history, online behavior, interest data, and interactions with our and other websites, applications, systems, and advertisements.

* Category G. Geolocation data, such as device location.

The categories of third parties to whom we disclosed personal information for a business or commercial purpose can be found under "[WHEN AND WITH WHOM DO WE SHARE YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?](#whoshare)".

**Your rights with respect to your personal data**

Right to request deletion of the data — Request to delete

You can ask for the deletion of your personal information. If you ask us to delete your personal information, we will respect your request and delete your personal information, subject to certain exceptions provided by law, such as (but not limited to) the exercise by another consumer of his or her right to free speech, our compliance requirements resulting from a legal obligation, or any processing that may be required to protect against illegal activities.

Right to be informed — Request to know

Depending on the circumstances, you have a right to know:

* whether we collect and use your personal information;

* the categories of personal information that we collect;

* the purposes for which the collected personal information is used;

* whether we sell your personal information to third parties;

* the categories of personal information that we sold or disclosed for a business purpose;

* the categories of third parties to whom the personal information was sold or disclosed for a business purpose; and

* the business or commercial purpose for collecting or selling personal information.

In accordance with applicable law, we are not obligated to provide or delete consumer information that is de-identified in response to a consumer request or to re-identify individual data to verify a consumer request.

Right to Non-Discrimination for the Exercise of a Consumer’s Privacy Rights

We will not discriminate against you if you exercise your privacy rights.

Verification process

Upon receiving your request, we will need to verify your identity to determine you are the same person about whom we have the information in our system. These verification efforts require us to ask you to provide information so that we can match it with information you have previously provided us. For instance, depending on the type of request you submit, we may ask you to provide certain information so that we can match the information you provide with the information we already have on file, or we may contact you through a communication method (e.g., phone or email) that you have previously provided to us. We may also use other verification methods as the circumstances dictate.

We will only use personal information provided in your request to verify your identity or authority to make the request. To the extent possible, we will avoid requesting additional information from you for the purposes of verification. However, if we cannot verify your identity from the information already maintained by us, we may request that you provide additional information for the purposes of verifying your identity and for security or fraud-prevention purposes. We will delete such additionally provided information as soon as we finish verifying you.

Other privacy rights

* You may object to the processing of your personal information.

* You may request correction of your personal data if it is incorrect or no longer relevant, or ask to restrict the processing of the information.

* You can designate an authorized agent to make a request under the CCPA on your behalf. We may deny a request from an authorized agent that does not submit proof that they have been validly authorized to act on your behalf in accordance with the CCPA.

* You may request to opt out from future selling of your personal information to third parties. Upon receiving an opt-out request, we will act upon the request as soon as feasibly possible, but no later than fifteen (15) days from the date of the request submission.

To exercise these rights, you can contact us by email at [\[email protected\]](https://www.100percentpure.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection), by visiting [https://www.100percentpure.com/pages/dsar-ccpa](https://www.100percentpure.com/pages/dsar-ccpa), or by referring to the contact details at the bottom of this document. If you have a complaint about how we handle your data, we would like to hear from you.

**13\. DO WE MAKE UPDATES TO THIS NOTICE?**

_**In Short:** Yes, we will update this notice as necessary to stay compliant with relevant laws._

We may update this privacy notice from time to time. The updated version will be indicated by an updated "Revised" date and the updated version will be effective as soon as it is accessible. If we make material changes to this privacy notice, we may notify you either by prominently posting a notice of such changes or by directly sending you a notification. We encourage you to review this privacy notice frequently to be informed of how we are protecting your information.

**14\. HOW CAN YOU CONTACT US ABOUT THIS NOTICE?**

If you have questions or comments about this notice, you may email us at [\[email protected\]](https://www.100percentpure.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection) or by post to:

Purity Cosmetics

2221 Oakland Road

San Jose, CA 95131

United States

If you are a resident in the European Economic Area, the "data controller" of your personal information is Purity Cosmetics. Purity Cosmetics has appointed Instant EU GDPR Representative Ltd to be its representative in the EEA. You can contact them directly regarding the processing of your information by Purity Cosmetics, by email at [\[email protected\]](https://www.100percentpure.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection), by visiting [https://gdprlocal.com](https://gdprlocal.com/), by phone at +353 15 549700, or by post to:

Instant EU GDPR Representative Ltd

Office 2 12A Lower Main Street

Lucan, Co. Dublin K78 X5P8

Ireland

**15\. HOW CAN YOU REVIEW, UPDATE, OR DELETE THE DATA WE COLLECT FROM YOU?**

Based on the applicable laws of your country, you may have the right to request access to the personal information we collect from you, change that information, or delete it. To request to review, update, or delete your personal information, please visit: [https://www.100percentpure.com/pages/dsar](https://www.100percentpure.com/pages/dsar).

------------------------------------------------------------------------------------

#### SUBSCRIBE

Get blog updates and exclusive discounts.

social-tiktok social-youtube

currency USD USD currency CAD CAD currency GBP GBP [MORE](#currencyPopWindow)

Got it

Choose Your Currency

currency USD United States dollar (USD)

currency CAD Canadian dollar (CAD)

currency BGN Bulgarian lev (BGN)

currency DKK Danish krone (DKK)

currency EUR Euro (EUR)

currency HUF Forint (HUF)

currency PLN Polish złoty (PLN)

currency GBP Pound sterling (GBP)

currency SEK Swedish krona (SEK)

currency CHF Swiss franc (CHF)

#### ABOUT

#### HELP

#### REWARDS

* |
* |

[Terms & Conditions](https://www.100percentpure.com/pages/terms-of-use) | [Privacy Policy](https://www.100percentpure.com/pages/privacy-policy) | [Cookie Policy](https://www.100percentpure.com/pages/cookie-policy) | Do Not Sell My Personal Information | ©2024 [100% PURE](https://www.100percentpure.com/)®

If you are using a screen reader and are having problems using this website, please call [+1 (844) 787-3100](tel:+18447873100) for assistance.

Country/region
--------------

Albania (ALL L) Andorra (EUR €) Austria (EUR €) Belgium (EUR €) Bosnia & Herzegovina (BAM КМ) Bulgaria (BGN лв.) Canada (CAD $) China (CNY ¥) Croatia (EUR €) Czechia (CZK Kč) Denmark (DKK kr.) Estonia (EUR €) Faroe Islands (DKK kr.) Finland (EUR €) France (EUR €) Gibraltar (GBP £) Greece (EUR €) Guernsey (GBP £) Hungary (HUF Ft) Iceland (ISK kr) Ireland (EUR €) Italy (EUR €) Jersey (USD $) Latvia (EUR €) Liechtenstein (CHF CHF) Lithuania (EUR €) Luxembourg (EUR €) Malta (EUR €) Moldova (MDL L) Monaco (EUR €) Montenegro (EUR €) Netherlands (EUR €) North Macedonia (USD $) Norway (USD $) Poland (PLN zł) Portugal (EUR €) Romania (RON Lei) San Marino (EUR €) Serbia (RSD РСД) Slovakia (EUR €) Slovenia (EUR €) Spain (EUR €) Sweden (SEK kr) Switzerland (CHF CHF) United Kingdom (GBP £) United States (USD $)

Update country/region

(CAD $)

 Search
